<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>daSWAG (Serverless Web Application Generator) on daSWAG</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in daSWAG (Serverless Web Application Generator) on daSWAG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&gt; daSWAG release v1.0.0-beta</title>
      <link>/release_notes/2019_08_30_daswag_1_0_0_beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/release_notes/2019_08_30_daswag_1_0_0_beta/</guid>
      <description>This is our first beta release for daSWAG v1.
Most important features  Create a new daSWAG project and initialize your user management component Add an Api or a Client component to your project.  How to install This is a beta release, so it is not available on our usual &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; release channel.
To install daSWAG v1.0.0-beta using NPM:
npm install -g daswag-cli@beta  Help and bugs If you find any issue with this release, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring a corporate proxy</title>
      <link>/setting_up_envrionment/configuring_corporate_proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/setting_up_envrionment/configuring_corporate_proxy/</guid>
      <description>When daSWAG is used in a company, you probably will need to configure all tools to bypass the corporate proxy.
You can try to configure the HTTP_PROXY and HTTPS_PROXY environment variables or use a tool like Cntlm.
But this probably won&amp;rsquo;t be enough, so you will need to configure separately all the tools that are used with daSWAG.
Introduction Supposing your proxy is defined with:
 username password host port  The resulting configuration is: http://username:password@host:port</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to our wonderful contributors  for making Open Source a better place! .ghContributors{ display:flex; flex-flow: wrap; align-content: flex-start }
.ghContributors &amp;gt; div{ width: 50% ; display: inline-flex; margin-bottom: 5px; } .ghContributors &amp;gt; div label{ padding-left: 4px ; } .ghContributors &amp;gt; div span{ font-size: x-small; padding-left: 4px ; }
  @stevehouel 1 commits</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Cloud provider account</title>
      <link>/setting_up_envrionment/using_cloud_account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/setting_up_envrionment/using_cloud_account/</guid>
      <description>The deployment of a serverless web application requires the use of an account on the target cloud service provider. The use of such services may generate costs at the end of the month depending on your use. That&amp;rsquo;s why, you will have to fill your credit card number when creating a cloud provider account. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, daSWAG makes maximum use of free tier services, allowing you to use your application in development and integration environments with complete peace of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>